The	O
execution	O
,	O
delivery	O
and	O
performance	O
of	O
the	O
Loan	O
Documents	O
have	O
been	O
duly	O
authorized	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
conflict	O
with	O
Borrower	B-PER
'	O
s	O
formation	O
documents	O
,	O
nor	O
constitute	O
an	O
event	O
of	O
default	O
under	O
any	O
material	O
agreement	O
by	O
which	O
Borrower	B-PER
is	O
bound	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
event	O
that	O
the	O
IL	O
Subsidiary	O
owns	O
any	O
other	O
assets	O
,	O
except	O
as	O
set	O
forth	O
herein	O
,	O
then	O
Borrower	B-PER
shall	O
notify	O
Lenders	O
and	O
at	O
Lenders	O
'	O
option	O
,	O
the	O
IL	O
Subsidiary	O
will	O
become	O
a	O
co	O
-	O
Borrower	B-PER
to	O
this	O
Agreement	O
and	O
shall	O
grant	O
a	O
first	O
priority	O
security	O
interest	O
in	O
all	O
assets	O
(	O
except	O
for	O
intellectual	O
property	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Agent	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
ratable	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Lenders	O
.	O

A	O
judgment	O
or	O
judgments	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
an	O
amount	O
,	O
individually	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
aggregate	O
,	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
Two	O
Hundred	O
Fifty	O
Thousand	O
Dollars	O
($	O
250	O
,	O
000	O
.	O
00	O
)	O
(	O
not	O
covered	O
by	O
independent	O
third	O
-	O
party	O
insurance	O
)	O
shall	O
be	O
rendered	O
against	O
Borrower	B-PER
and	O
shall	O
remain	O
unsatisfied	O
or	O
unstayed	O
for	O
a	O
period	O
of	O
thirty	O
(	O
30	O
)	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
entry	O
thereof	O
(	O
provided	O
that	O
no	O
Credit	O
Extensions	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
or	O
stay	O
of	O
such	O
judgment	O
);	O
8	O
.	O
8	O
Misrepresentations	O
.	O

Any	O
proceeds	O
of	O
insurance	O
maintained	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
pursuant	O
to	O
this	O
Section	O
and	O
received	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
will	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
Bank	B-ORG
,	O
promptly	O
upon	O
their	O
receipt	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
.	O

"	O
CREDIT	O
EXTENSION	O
"	O
is	O
each	O
Equipment	O
Advance	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
extension	O
of	O
credit	O
by	O
Bank	B-ORG
for	O
Borrower	B-PER
'	O
s	O
benefit	O
.	O

Effective	O
only	O
when	O
an	O
Event	O
of	O
Default	O
occurs	O
and	O
continues	O
,	O
Borrower	B-PER
irrevocably	O
appoints	O
Bank	B-ORG
as	O
its	O
lawful	O
attorney	O
to	O
:	O
(	O
i	O
)	O
transfer	O
the	O
Collateral	O
into	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Bank	B-ORG
or	O
a	O
third	O
party	O
as	O
the	O
Code	O
permits	O
.	O

Section	O
10	O
.	O
12	O
Limited	O
Nature	O
of	O
Company	O
'	O
s	O
Obligations	O
;	O
Pittston	B-ORG
Terminal	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
Liability	O
for	O
Obligations	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
Certain	O
Decisions	O
Regarding	O
the	O
Bonds	O
.	O

The	O
systems	O
of	O
conveyors	O
leading	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
yard	O
storage	O
are	O
controlled	O
from	O
a	O
central	B-LOC
control	I-LOC
room	I-LOC
atop	I-LOC
transfer	I-LOC
tower	I-LOC
TT2	I-LOC
or	O
from	O
other	O
computer	O
sites	O
.	O

"	O
IL	O
Subsidiary	O
"	O
means	O
,	O
Vringo	B-ORG
(	O
Israel	B-LOC
)	O
Ltd	O
.	O
"	O
Indebtedness	O
"	O
is	O
(	O
a	O
)	O
indebtedness	O
for	O
borrowed	O
money	O
or	O
the	O
deferred	O
price	O
of	O
property	O
or	O
services	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
reimbursement	O
and	O
other	O
obligations	O
for	O
surety	O
bonds	O
and	O
letters	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
(	O
b	O
)	O
obligations	O
evidenced	O
by	O
notes	O
,	O
bonds	O
,	O
debentures	O
or	O
similar	O
instruments	O
,	O
(	O
c	O
)	O
capital	O
lease	O
obligations	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
d	O
)	O
Contingent	O
Obligations	O
.	O

9	O
.	O
2	O
This	O
Agreement	O
shall	O
be	O
written	O
in	O
both	O
Chinese	B-MISC
and	O
English	B-MISC
language	O
in	O
two	O
copies	O
,	O
The	O
Parties	O
hereto	O
shall	O
execute	O
two	O
originals	O
of	O
this	O
Agreement	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
each	O
party	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
original	O
shall	O
have	O
equal	O
legal	O
validity	O
.	O

