Borrower	B-PER
does	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
stock	O
,	O
partnership	O
interest	O
or	O
other	O
equity	O
securities	O
except	O
for	O
Permitted	O
Investments	O
.	O

If	O
any	O
new	O
law	O
or	O
regulation	O
increases	O
Agent	O
and	O
/	O
or	O
Lenders	O
'	O
costs	O
or	O
reduces	O
its	O
income	O
for	O
any	O
loan	O
,	O
Borrower	B-PER
shall	O
pay	O
the	O
increase	O
in	O
cost	O
or	O
reduction	O
in	O
income	O
or	O
additional	O
;	O
provided	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
Borrower	B-PER
shall	O
not	O
be	O
liable	O
for	O
any	O
amount	O
attributable	O
to	O
any	O
period	O
before	O
one	O
hundred	O
eighty	O
(	O
180	O
)	O
days	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
date	O
Agent	O
notifies	O
Borrower	B-PER
of	O
such	O
increased	O
costs	O
.	O

Bank	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
appointment	O
as	O
Borrower	B-PER
'	O
s	O
attorney	O
in	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
Bank	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
rights	O
and	O
powers	O
,	O
coupled	O

None	O
of	O
the	O
components	O
of	O
the	O
Collateral	O
shall	O
be	O
maintained	O
at	O
locations	O
other	O
than	O
as	O
provided	O
in	O
the	O
Perfection	O
Certificate	O
or	O
as	O
Borrower	B-PER
has	O
given	O
Agent	O
notice	O
pursuant	O
to	O
Section	O
7	O
.	O
2	O
.	O

"	O
SUBORDINATED	O
DEBT	O
"	O
is	O
debt	O
incurred	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
subordinated	O
to	O
Borrowers	O
debt	O
to	O
Bank	B-ORG
(	O
and	O
identified	O
as	O
subordinated	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
and	O
Bank	B-ORG
).	O

The	O
systems	O
of	O
conveyors	O
leading	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
yard	O
storage	O
are	O
controlled	O
from	O
a	O
central	B-LOC
control	I-LOC
room	I-LOC
atop	I-LOC
transfer	I-LOC
tower	I-LOC
TT2	I-LOC
or	O
from	O
other	O
computer	O
sites	O
.	O

Box	O
2681GT	O
,	O
George	B-LOC
Town	I-LOC
,	O
Grand	B-LOC
Cayman	I-LOC
,	O
British	B-LOC
West	I-LOC
Indies	I-LOC
,	O
hereinafter	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
"	O
Company	O
";	O
Airland	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Limited	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
corporation	O
incorporated	O
under	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
the	O
British	B-LOC
Virgin	I-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
,	O
whose	O
registered	O
address	O
is	O
2nd	B-LOC
floor	I-LOC
,	O
Abbott	B-LOC
Building	I-LOC
Road	I-LOC
Town	I-LOC
,	O
Tortola	B-LOC
,	O
British	B-LOC
Virgin	I-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
,	O
hereinafter	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
"	O
Airland	O
";	O
AND	O
Bizexpress	B-LOC
Limited	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
corporation	O
incorporated	O
under	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
the	O
British	B-LOC
Virgin	I-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
,	O
whose	O
registered	O
address	O
is	O
2nd	B-LOC
floor	I-LOC
,	O
Abbott	B-LOC
Building	I-LOC
Road	I-LOC
Town	I-LOC
,	O
Tortola	B-LOC
,	O
British	B-LOC
Virgin	I-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
,	O
hereinafter	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
"	O
Bizexpress	B-ORG
"	O
Airland	B-ORG
and	O
Bizexpress	B-ORG
are	O
collectively	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
"	O
Borrower	B-PER
".	O

The	O
issuance	O
of	O
the	O
Bonds	O
will	O
not	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
or	O
contingently	O
obligate	O
the	O
Issuer	O
,	O
the	O
Commonwealth	B-LOC
or	O
any	O
of	O
its	O
political	O
subdivisions	O
to	O
levy	O
or	O
pledge	O
any	O
form	O
of	O
taxation	O
whatever	O
or	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
appropriation	O
for	O
their	O
payment	O
.	O

9	O
.	O
2	O
This	O
Agreement	O
shall	O
be	O
written	O
in	O
both	O
Chinese	B-MISC
and	O
English	B-MISC
language	O
in	O
two	O
copies	O
,	O
The	O
Parties	O
hereto	O
shall	O
execute	O
two	O
originals	O
of	O
this	O
Agreement	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
each	O
party	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
original	O
shall	O
have	O
equal	O
legal	O
validity	O
.	O

