Borrower	B-PER
will	O
make	O
payments	O
monthly	O
in	O
advance	O
of	O
principal	O
and	O
accrued	O
interest	O
for	O
each	O
Equipment	O
Advance	O
(	O
collectively	O
,	O
"	O
Scheduled	O
Payments	O
"),	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Business	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
following	O
the	O
Funding	O
Date	O
(	O
or	O
commencing	O
on	O
the	O
Funding	O
Date	O
if	O
the	O
Funding	O
Date	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
Business	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
)	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
such	O
Equipment	O
Advance	O
and	O
continuing	O
thereafter	O
during	O
the	O
Repayment	O
Period	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Business	O
Day	O
of	O
each	O
calendar	O
month	O
(	O
each	O
a	O
"	O
Payment	O
Date	O
"),	O
in	O
an	O
amount	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
Loan	O
Factor	O
multiplied	O
by	O
the	O
Loan	O
Amount	O
for	O
such	O
Equipment	O
Advance	O
as	O
of	O
such	O
Payment	O
Date	O
.	O

BORROWER	B-PER
AND	O
BANK	B-ORG
EACH	O
HEREBY	O
WAIVE	O
THEIR	O
RESPECTIVE	O
RIGHTS	O
TO	O
A	O
JURY	O
TRIAL	O
OF	O
ANY	O
CLAIM	O
OR	O
CAUSE	O
OF	O
ACTION	O
BASED	O
UPON	O
OR	O
ARISING	O
OUT	O
OF	O
ANY	O
OF	O
THE	O
LOAN	O
DOCUMENTS	O
OR	O
ANY	O
OF	O
THE	O
TRANSACTIONS	O
CONTEMPLATED	O
THEREIN	O
,	O
INCLUDING	O

/	O
s	O
/	O
Bing	B-PER
Yu	I-PER
Name	O
:	O

It	O
is	O
specifically	O
understood	O
and	O
agreed	O
that	O
the	O
liability	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
is	O
limited	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
'	O
s	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
obligations	O
of	O
Pittston	B-ORG
Coal	I-ORG
Terminal	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
to	O
make	O
payments	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Bonds	O
under	O
Section	O
3	O
.	O
2	O
(	O
a	O
)(	O
ix	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Throughput	O
Agreement	O
and	O
is	O
payable	O
solely	O
from	O
those	O
payments	O
and	O
collateral	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
,	O
specifically	O
pledged	O
for	O
such	O
purpose	O
.	O

"	O
PRIME	O
RATE	O
"	O
is	O
Bank	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
most	O
recently	O
announced	O
"	O
prime	O
rate	O
,"	O
even	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
Bank	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
lowest	O
rate	O
.	O

All	O
amendments	O
to	O
this	O
Agreement	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
writing	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
Borrower	B-PER
and	O
Bank	B-ORG
.	O

"	O
Code	O
"	O
is	O
the	O
Uniform	O
Commercial	O
Code	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
same	O
may	O
,	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
be	O
enacted	O
and	O
in	O
effect	O
in	O
the	O
Commonwealth	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Massachusetts	I-LOC
;	O
provided	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
extent	O
that	O
the	O
Code	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
define	O
any	O
term	O
herein	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
Loan	O
Document	O
and	O
such	O
term	O
is	O
defined	O
differently	O
in	O
different	O
Articles	O
or	O
Divisions	O
of	O
the	O
Code	O
,	O
the	O
definition	O
of	O
such	O
term	O
contained	O
in	O
Article	O
or	O
Division	O
9	O
shall	O
govern	O
;	O
provided	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
event	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
mandatory	O
provisions	O
of	O
law	O
,	O
any	O
or	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
attachment	O
,	O
perfection	O
,	O
or	O
priority	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
remedies	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
,	O
Agent	O
'	O
s	O
and	O
Lenders	O
'	O
Lien	O
on	O
any	O
Collateral	O
is	O
governed	O
by	O
the	O
Uniform	O
Commercial	O
Code	O
in	O
effect	O
in	O
a	O
jurisdiction	O
other	O
than	O
the	O
Commonwealth	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Massachusetts	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
term	O
"	O
Code	O
"	O
shall	O
mean	O
the	O
Uniform	O
Commercial	O
Code	O
as	O
enacted	O
and	O
in	O
effect	O
in	O
such	O
other	O
jurisdiction	O
solely	O
for	O
purposes	O
on	O
the	O
provisions	O
thereof	O
relating	O
to	O
such	O
attachment	O
,	O
perfection	O
,	O
priority	O
,	O
or	O
remedies	O
and	O
for	O
purposes	O
of	O
definitions	O
relating	O
to	O
such	O
provisions	O
.	O

Gold	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
Venture	I-LOC
Lending	I-LOC
03	I-LOC
,	O
L	O
.	O
P	O
.	O

The	O
Company	O
will	O
maintain	O
its	O
existence	O
as	O
a	O
general	O
partnership	O
under	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
the	O
Commonwealth	B-LOC
and	O
will	O
not	O
merge	O
or	O
consolidate	O
with	O
,	O
or	O
sell	O
or	O
otherwise	O
transfer	O
to	O
another	O
legal	O
entity	O
all	O
or	O
substantially	O
all	O
of	O
its	O
assets	O
as	O
an	O
entirety	O
and	O
/	O
or	O
dissolve	O
unless	O
(	O
i	O
)	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
surviving	O
,	O
resulting	O
or	O
transferee	O
legal	O
entity	O
organized	O
and	O
existing	O
under	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
,	O
any	O
state	O
or	O
the	O
District	O
of	O
Columbia	B-LOC
,	O
which	O
is	O
solvent	O
and	O
(	O
if	O
not	O
the	O
Company	O
)	O
assumes	O
in	O
writing	O
all	O
the	O
obligations	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
under	O
this	O
Loan	O
Agreement	O
and	O
(	O
ii	O
)	O
the	O
Company	O
or	O
the	O
surviving	O
or	O
transferee	O
entity	O
is	O
not	O
immediately	O
after	O
such	O
merger	O
,	O
consolidation	O
or	O
transfer	O
in	O
default	O
in	O
any	O
material	O
respect	O
under	O
this	O
Loan	O
Agreement	O
;	O
provided	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
construed	O
as	O
prohibiting	O
changes	O
in	O
the	O
ownership	O
interests	O
of	O
the	O
Partners	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O

9	O
.	O
2	O
This	O
Agreement	O
shall	O
be	O
written	O
in	O
both	O
Chinese	B-MISC
and	O
English	B-MISC
language	O
in	O
two	O
copies	O
,	O
The	O
Parties	O
hereto	O
shall	O
execute	O
two	O
originals	O
of	O
this	O
Agreement	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
each	O
party	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
original	O
shall	O
have	O
equal	O
legal	O
validity	O
.	O

